Darin Chau Yu Foon

⊠ darinchauyf@gmail.com

• https://github.com/darinchau

\cdots: +852 5661 8566

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/darinchauyf/

Hi! I am Darin. I am a mathematics and computer science undergraduate student from HKUST. I have conducted research in mathematics and computer science for the past two years. I can also do python and Javascript programming. In my free time I love to play classical music on the piano.



EDUCATION

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

BSc in Mathematics and Computer Science; GPA: 3.84

Hong Kong Sep 2020 - Present

SELECTED COURSE WORK

• COMP2211: Exploring AI (Grade: A+)

• MATH2431: Honors Probability (Grade: A)

• MATH4141: Number Theory and Applications (Grade: A)

• MATH5111: Advanced Algebra I (Grade: A)

EXPERIENCE

Math Research

Supervisor: Prof. Ivan Ip

Hong Kong

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

- Cluster algebra: (Algebraic Geometry/Algebraic Combinatorics Math) We investigated the positivity theorem of cluster algebras and the combinatorial tools developed by Gross et. al. for the proof.
- **TikzPaint**: We developed TikzPaint, a Python Library for generating tikz code and animations, to demonstrate high-dimensional plots and figures in the research

Computer Science Research

Hong Kong

Supervisor: Prof. Gary Chan Sheung-Han

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- **PHNet**: We investigated the Parasite-Host CNN model developed by Meng et. al. for video crowd counting. We developed a synthetic dataset and suggested modified model structures.
- Unity Dataset: We developed a synthetic dataset consisting of videos of a crowd in Unity3D. This provides a 4k dataset for crowd counting research.

Youthniverse

Hong Kong

Software Developer

Aug 2020 - Feb 2021

- o Duties: Developed a profile matching mobile application for a startup non-profit organization using React Native.
- AI profile matching: Developed the AI-powered algorithm for profile matching using regression techniques and clustering.

Music is the Key

Hong Kong

Software Developer

Aug 2021 - Aug 2022

• **Duties**: To develop softwares and chat bots to enhance online user experience in an international organization focusing on music education and networking.

PROJECTS

• TikzPaint: Open source python library for generating high-dimensional mathematical figures.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- Languages: Python, Javascript, C++, C#, Rust
- Tools (Machine Learning): PyTorch, Numpy, Keras, TensorFlow, Pandas, MatPlotLib
- Tools (App development): React, Angular, Firebase, Unity3D